velocify.com 2015-06-24

# Privacy - Velocify: High Performance Sales

Our privacy policy is pretty simple. We will only contact you if you voluntarily submit your contact information. We will never sell your information.

If you would like all of the details, read on.

## Velocify Incorporated Global Privacy Policy

Velocify Incorporated (“Velocify”) respects your right to privacy. This policy summarizes what personally identifiable information we may collect, and how we might use this information. This policy also describes other important topics relating to your privacy. It is Velocify policy to comply with all applicable privacy and data protection laws. This commitment reflects the value we place on earning and keeping the trust of our employees, customers, business partners and others who share their personal information with us. This Global Privacy Policy (this “Policy”) describes how Velocify protects your privacy when we collect personal information on Velocify Internet sites. As used in this Policy, the term “personal information” means information that identifies you personally, alone or in combination with other information available to us.

### Your Consent

By visiting a Velocify website or providing personal information to us, you are consenting to the collection, use and disclosure of your personal information as described in this Policy. If you do not consent to the collection, use and disclosure of your personal information as described in this Policy (and any applicable Country or Web Site Privacy Statements), do not use Velocify Internet Sites, contact Velocify, or Submit Data to Velocify via Internet form. Limitations on the Collection, Use and Disclosure of Personal Information To the extent required by applicable law, whenever Velocify collects personal information on a Velocify Internet Site, Velocify will:

  * provide timely and appropriate notice to you about its data practices;
  * collect, use, disclose and transfer your personal information only with your consent, which may be express or implied, depending on the sensitivity of the personal information, legal requirements, and other factors;
  * collect your personal information only for specific, limited purposes. The information we collect will be relevant, adequate and not excessive for the purposes for which it is collected;
  * process your personal information in a manner consistent with the purposes for which it was originally collected or to which you have subsequently consented;
  * take commercially reasonable steps to ensure that your personal information is reliable for its intended use, accurate, complete, and, where necessary, kept up-to-date;

### Information Collected on Velocify Internet Sites and How It May Be Used

When you access and use a Velocify Internet Site, there are 3 ways we may collect information about you:

### 1\. Information Sent to Us by Your Web Browser

Velocify collects information that is sent to us automatically by your web browser. This information typically includes the IP address of your Internet service provider, the name of your operating system (such as Macintosh ® or Windows ®) and the name and version of your browser (such as Internet Explorer ® or FireFox ®). The information we receive depends on the settings on your web browser. Please check your browser if you want to learn what information your browser sends or how to change your settings. The information provided by your browser does not identify you personally. We use this information to create statistics that help us improve our sites and make them more compatible with the technology used by our Internet visitors

### 2\. Information Collected By Placing a “Cookie” On Your Computer

Velocify may obtain information about you by installing a “tag” on your computer’s hard drive. This tag is known as a “cookie.” All of our Velocify Internet Sites use “session cookies.” A session cookie is used to tag your computer with a computer-generated, unique identifier when you access our site. A session cookie does not identify you personally and expires after you close your browser. We use session cookies to collect statistical information about the ways visitors use our sites’ which pages they visit, which links they use, and how long they stay on each page. We analyze this information in statistical form to better understand our visitor’s interests and needs to improve the content and functionality of our sites.

Some Velocify Internet sites also use “persistent cookies.” These cookies do not expire when you close your browser; they stay on your computer until you delete them. By assigning your computer a unique identifier, we are able to create a database of your previous choices and preferences, and in situations where these choices or preferences need to be collected again, they can be provided by us automatically, saving you time and effort.

If you do not wish to receive cookies, you may set your browser to reject cookies or to alert you when a cookie is placed on your computer. Although you are not required to accept cookies when you visit a Velocify Internet Site, you may be unable to use all of the functionality of the site if your browser rejects our cookies.

### 3\. Information You Knowingly and Voluntarily Provide

Velocify collects the information you knowingly and voluntarily provide when you use a Velocify Internet Site, for example, the information you provide when you sign up to receive email alerts, when you complete a survey, or when you ask us a question or email us with feedback. In many cases this information will be personal information. Velocify uses this information for the purposes for which you provide it. We may also use the information we collect on Velocify Internet Sites for various business purposes such as customer service, fraud prevention, market research, improving our products and services, and providing you and your company with information and offers we believe may be of interest to you. We may also remove all the personally identifiable information and use the rest for historical, statistical or scientific purposes.

### Sharing Personal Information

Velocify will not sell personal information collected from its Internet sites to mailing list brokers or other third parties. Velocify may share your personal information with third parties we hire to perform services for us. These third parties are required to use the personal information we share with them only to perform services on our behalf and to treat your personal information as strictly confidential. In some cases, Velocify may share your personal information with third parties who partner with us to provide products and services to our customers. When we do so, we will require our business partners to use the personal information we share with them in a manner consistent with the purposes for which it was originally collected (or to which you subsequently consented) and only as permitted under this Policy, any applicable Country or Web Site Privacy Statements, and all applicable privacy and data protection laws. In certain, limited circumstances we may share or transfer personal information to unrelated third parties. For example, we may provide personal information to a third party (i) at your request; (ii) to comply with a legal requirement or court order; (iii) to investigate a possible crime, such as identity theft; (iv) in connection with the sale, purchase, merger, reorganization, liquidation or dissolution of Velocify or a Velocify business unit; or (v) under similar circumstances. If such an event occurs, we will take appropriate steps to protect your personal information.

### Security of Personal Information

Your personal information will generally be stored in Velocify databases or databases maintained by our service providers. Most of these databases are stored on servers located in the United States. To the extent required by law, if your personal information will be transferred outside your country an appropriate notice will be provided. Velocify maintains reasonable safeguards to protect the confidentiality, security and integrity of your personal information. For example, we use secure socket layer (SSL) technology to transfer personal information over the Internet. Although we use security measures to help protect your personal information against unauthorized disclosure, misuse or alteration, as is the case with all computer networks linked to the Internet, we cannot guarantee the security of information provided over the Internet and will not be responsible for breaches of security beyond our reasonable control.

### Links to Third Party Internet Sites

Velocify Internet Sites may contain links to Internet sites that are not operated by Velocify. These links are provided as a service and do not imply any endorsement of the activities or content of these sites, nor any association with their operators. Velocify does not control these Internet sites and is not responsible for their content, security, or privacy practices. We urge you to review the privacy policy posted on web sites you visit before using the site or providing personal information. Access to Personal Information You may review, correct and update the personal information that you provide to us by writing to us at Velocify, Global Privacy Policy, 222 North Sepulveda Blvd. 18th Floor, El Segundo, CA 90245, USA.

### Retention of Personal Information

Velocify retains the personal information collected on Velocify Internet Sites as long as necessary to provide the services, products and information you request or as permitted by applicable law. Questions about this Policy or our Privacy Statements If you have any questions about this Policy or our use of your personal information, please write to us at Velocify, Global Privacy Policy, 222 North Sepulveda Blvd. 18th Floor, El Segundo, CA 90245, USA.

### Changes to this Policy

Velocify reserves the right, at its sole discretion, to change, modify, add or remove any portion of this policy, in whole or in part, at any time. Changes in Policy will be effective when posted. You agree to review this Policy periodically to be aware of any changes. Your continued use of the Site after any changes to this Policy will be considered acceptance of those changes.
